

OLCAY TAPAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



U ⊠ o

+46 073 600 6087

olcaytapan10@gmail.com

lundby, Göteborg

https://github.com/Olcaytp

in

http://www.linkedin.com/in/olcaytapan

https://olcaytapan-portfolio.netlify.app/

ABOUT ME

I am a hardworking Computer Engineer and Civil Engineer. I am always interested in technological innovations. At the first opportunity, I switched careers to software development.

I've worked mostly with JavaScript and Angular to build user-friendly websites and applications. Additionaly, I've been developing full stack ecommerce projects with using C# & ASP .NET Core lately due to my great interest in the backend.

EDUCATION

Ahmet Yesevi University Anadolu University

Bachelor of Computer Bachelor of Civil Engineering Engineering Engineering(%100 English)

2020 - 2023 2011 - 2016

SKILLS

-Javascript -JQuery

-Angular -C/C++

-HTML5 / CSS -C#

-Vs Code -ASP.NET

-MsSQL -Bootstrap

-Postman -Git / Github

-MongoDB -FireBase

COURSES & BOOTCAMPS

Web and Multimedia Developer Specialist Jan 2023 - Feb 2023 Bootcamp

Mext Bilisim

- -Web Application Development Fundamentals
- -Frontend Development
- -Backend Devlopment
- -Web Infrastructure, Web Security

Udemy Jan 2022 - Present

- -Angular The Complete Guide 2022 Udemy (Maximilian Schwarzmüller)
- -MEAN Stack E-Commerce App: Angular 14, NX, PrimeNg [2022]
- -Angular & NodeJS The Mean Stack Guide 2022 Udemy (Maximilian Schwarzmüller)

Angular Bootcamp Feb 2022 - Apr 2022

Orion Innovation Turkey

- -Javascript
- -TypeScript
- -Angular Structure
- -Building Forms
- -Building Angular Project

Ecole 42 (International Software School)

Comprehensive Software Education Program

- -Shell Linux Tutorial
- -C Language Functions Projects
- -Basic Software Logic Trainings

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer - Intern

Cubicl / Ankara-Remote

09/22-02/23

During this productive internship process, I contributed to my development by performing tasks in the following areas:

- -Application Interface Design Fix
- -Form Field Improvement
- -Creating and Designing a New Page
- -Fix bugs in the app

Civil Engineer

Turkey 2016-2021

Within the scope of civil engineering, my responsibilities as a field engineer in the construction, repair and renovation projects of structures such as hospitals, hotels, chain markets and villas;

- -Quality control
- -Manufacturing inspection
- -Work follow

Nov 2021 - Oct 2022

-Progress and quantity